Daniel Miller

Phone: 02102795545

Email: daniel.miller.djm@gmail.com

I'm a highly motivated individual with a deep interest in technology and computing. My most recent interest has been game design within UE4 and Unity. I study software engineering at Victoria University of Wellington, with ambitions to gain experience in industry before starting my own company.

Technical Skills

- 2 Years Java (University)
- 1 Year C/C++ (University)
- 6 Months Python (University)
- 6 Months HTML, CSS & JavaScript (University)
- Advanced skills on both windows and Linux computers

Transferable Skills

Team Player: Worked within the Bay Four Square team from 2015 - 2018, and have experience in group projects at university in courses ENGR 101, ENGR 110 and SWEN 225.

Highly Organised: Consistently use good design principles and version control in programming tasks to organise source code.

Fast Learner: Became proficient with sales methods at JB Hi-Fi very quickly, resulting in similar sales figures to full-time staff within the first week.

Problem Solver: Have been challenged by a wide range of programming tasks over the last two years, requiring abstract and critical thinking to complete.

Client/Customer Interaction: Have excellent communication skills, and experience interacting with customers at JB Hi-Fi.

Education

2017 - 2020: Victoria University of Wellington - Bachelor of Engineering with Honours - BE(Hons), Majoring in Software Engineering.

2012 - 2016: Kerikeri High School.

Work Experience

Summer Work in 2018 - Present: JB Hi-Fi

Salesperson at JB Hi-Fi specialising in IT related products. Responsibilities include interacting with customers and setting up sales.

Summer Work in 2015 - 2018: Bay Four Square

Floor worker at Bay Four Square, Responsibilities included point of sale and shelf restocking.

Hobbies and Interests

Skiing: Passionate about skiing, and ski on the Whakapapa ski field regularly during the winter season.

Movies: Love movies and TV shows, and have an interest in the behind the scenes processes which go on to develop them.

Computers and Games: Have a interest in computers and both playing/designing games.

	_ 4	_				25
$\boldsymbol{-}$	ΔT	Ω.	ro	n	c	20
1	CI	G			L	

Name	Relationship	Phone
Emmett Morris	Store Manager, JB Hi-Fi Wellington 2018-Present	021 180 0049
Wendy Porter	Employer, Bay Four Square 2015-2018	021 241 4815
Vince Exconde	Residential Advisor in 2017	021 059 1264